(Sheldon:)You're a real catch compared
to some snoring guy...
(Sheldon:)...with a fridge full of lousy grapes.
(Leonard:)None of this matters.
(Leonard:)I trust that Penny cares about me
and nothing's gonna happen with this guy.
(Sheldon:)Unless of course he's a skilled hypnotist.
(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)While unlikely,
it's still a statistical possibility.
(Sheldon:)She might be performing sexual acts
with him and not even know it.
- Now you're just being ridiculous.
- Am I?
(Sheldon:)The mind's a mysterious thing, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)He could be having the time of his life...
(Sheldon:)...while she thinks she's a chicken
pecking for corn.
(Raj:)Look at us, sneaking around in the middle
of the night like a couple of cat burglars.
(Howard:)I think we're more like ninjas.